

28/09/1993

# **KIEU CONG DUY THAI**

Sales B2B

As a highly motivated and results-driven Sale / Pre-Sale with 7 years of experience, I am committed to delivering exceptional results and driving business growth. I possess a strongunderstanding of business processes, data analysis, and projectmanagement, as well as excellent communication and stakeholdermanagement skills.

#### **EXPERTISE**

**Business Analysis Skills** 

(IIBA BABOK v3.0)

Planning

Presentation

Leaddership

Time Management

C# Foundation

SQL Foundation

### **EDUCATION**

2015 - 2017

**HUTECH University** 

Bachelor of Business Administration 3.95/4 GPA

2011 - 2014

Saigon International University

Diploma of Business Administration 3.0/4 GPA

#### LANGUAGE

**English** 

- IELTS 6.5
- TOEIC 700

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

2021 - Present

**Sales Executive** 

Rotomatik Vietnam

Focused on the Lifting Truck domain and business administration. I worked closely with stakeholders, analyzed customer demand, and developed new payment systems. Additionally, I drew blueprints for warehouse systems, collaborating with customers. I worked alongside a team of 20 members.

2019 - 2021

**Business Development** 

**OV** Logistics

Logistics-focused Business Development professional, successfully developed payment systems, collaborated with customers for scheduling and coordination, and led a team of 20 for project success

## CERTIFICATE

**IMIC Business Analysis** 

BABOK v3.0 2022

#### 2017 - 2020 **Business Analyst**

STAR Education

Collaborated with high schools and universities to teach soft skills to students, handled business flow, and prepared lessons for supporting teams. I operated classes in the Star Education center and worked with a Dev Team outsourcing to build a website. Additionally, I worked with the BOD in presales activities, particularly in the analysis phase. I also worked on-site with clients to develop new markets that aligned with the company's strategy.

#### CONTACT



0902 389 290



kieuthai2809@gmail.com



X 73/18 Pham Van Chieu, Ward 14, Go Vap District.